tmiwireless.com 2011-06-07

# Privacy

### Privacy Policy

tmiWireless.com takes personal privacy very seriously and is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitor's personally identifiable information. We have created this Privacy Policy document to help you understand the type of information and data we collect on our website, and how that information is used. 

#### Ordering Products through our Website

When you decide to order a product featured on our website such as a cell phone with service plan activation, you will be redirected to the merchant website through which that product is fulfilled. In some cases the merchant's website will be "co-branded" with our logo. This co-branded website is operated completely by the merchant, independently from tmiWireless.com, and collects personally identifiable information directly from you when you submit your order. tmiWireless.com does not capture order information including any personally identifiable information from you. Some merchants may provide sales reporting to tmiWireless.com that includes limited personal information such as your name, the date of your order, the product you ordered, and the status of the order. Please note that each merchant featured on this site has their own privacy policy and we recommend you read the merchant's privacy policy before submitting your order. tmiWireless.com is not responsible for the effectiveness of any merchant's privacy policy. For your convenience, we have included links to the privacy policy documents hosted by each merchant featured on our website. 

  * **Cell Phones and Wireless Devices requiring Plan Activation**
    * Simplexity (cellstores.com) - <https://www.cellstores.com/help/privacy_fs.asp?referringdomain=cellstores.com>
    * LetsTalk - <http://www.letstalk.com/about/security1.htm>
    * AT&T Mobility - <http://www.wireless.att.com/privacy/>
  * **Wireless Accessories**
    * Cellphoneshop.net - <http://www.cellphoneshop.net/privacypolicy.html>
  * **Satellite TV Services**
    * VMC Satellite - <http://www.vmcsatellite.com/red_design/privacy_policy.htm>
    * Cannon Satellite - <http://www.cannonsatellite.com/PrivacyPolicy.cfm>

#### Email Communication (Newsletters, Alerts, Notifications, Announcements, etc)

Our website may offer free newsletter subscriptions, offer alerts, weekly specials, and other free services that require your email address for communication. If you explicitly opt in to any of these services, you will receive the requested content via email to the email address you provide at the time of registration. Your email address will not be sold, rented, or given to any third party organization. You may discontinue receiving any email communication to which you have subscribed by using the unsubscribe links or methods described at the bottom of each email. If you place an order through one of the merchants featured on our website, please read their privacy policies regarding how they use your email address after you have submitted your order. 

#### Cookies

"A cookie is a small string of text stored on a user's computer by a web browser. A cookie consists of one or more name-value pairs containing bits of information such as user preferences, shopping cart contents, the identifier for a server-based session, or other data used by websites." (The preceeding quote was take from the definition of a browser cookie at [Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). We make use of cookies on our website for various purposes including website display optimization, order tracking, user preferences, content filtering, and other purposes as needed. 

#### Website Traffic Data

Our website is hosted on a web server that maintains log files that record website traffic data. When a visitor accesses any resource on our website such as a web page, an image, or any other piece of information published on our site, the web server will record various technical information about the visitor's request in this log file. Some information recorded includes the visitor's: time of request, requested URL, IP address, browser type, referring website URL, operating system, and cookie data. We may use the data in these log files to analyze our users' behavior for the purpose of improving the website and the experience in future versions of our website. In the rare cases of suspected fraudulent or criminal activity, we may also use the log file data as needed to help authorities or impacted organizations. 

#### Disclaimer

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us via the methods described on our customer service page.

|   
---|---
